workflowmax.com 2019-07-12

# Privacy Notice | Xero AU

##  How we collect your data 

When you visit our websites or use our services, we collect personal data. The ways we collect it can be broadly categorised into the following:

**Information you provide to us directly:** When you visit or use some parts of our websites and/or services we might ask you to provide personal data to us. For example, we ask for your contact information when you sign up for a free trial, respond to a job application or an email offer, participate in community forums, join us on social media, take part in training and events, contact us with questions or request support. If you don’t want to provide us with personal data, you don’t have to, but it might mean you can’t use some parts of our websites or services.

**Information we collect automatically:** We collect some information about you automatically when you visit our websites or use our services, like your IP address and device type. We also collect information when you navigate through our websites and services, including what pages you looked at and what links you clicked on. This information is useful for us as it helps us get a better understanding of how you’re using our websites and services so that we can continue to provide the best experience possible (e.g., by personalising the content you see).

Some of this information is collected using cookies and similar tracking technologies. If you want to find out more about the types of cookies we use, why, and how you can control them, take a look at our cookie notice.

**Information we get from third parties:** The majority of information we collect, we collect directly from you. Sometimes we might collect personal data about you from other sources, such as publicly available materials or trusted third parties like our marketing and research partners. We use this information to supplement the personal data we already hold about you, in order to better inform, personalise and improve our services, and to validate the personal data you provide.

Where we collect personal data, we’ll only process it:

  * to perform a contract with you, or
  * where we have legitimate interests to process the personal data and they’re not overridden by your rights, or
  * in accordance with a legal obligation, or 
  * where we have your consent.

If we don’t collect your personal data, we may be unable to provide you with all our services, and some functions and features on our websites may not be available to you.   

If you’re someone who doesn’t have a relationship with us, but believe that a Xero subscriber has entered your personal data into our websites or services, you’ll need to contact that Xero subscriber for any questions you have about your personal data (including where you want to access, correct, amend, or request that the user delete, your personal data).
